Guide to the Larry Kramer Papers YCAL MSS 722
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- October 2008 Acquisition, circa 1916-2008; 344633; 100.63 Linear Feet (117 boxes) + 2 broadside folders, 8 rolls, 2 record albums
  This portion of the collection consists of an extensive amount of drafts and manuscripts of and files relating to Larry Kramer's writings, including plays, screenplays, and books. Also found is correspondence, printed material, notes, and other files, stemming from Kramer's film work in the 1960s and 1970s, his AIDS advocacy and activism from the late 1970s to the present day, his AIDS-related research, and other professional activities. There are also some personal and family papers. This portion of the collection originated from Kramer's apartment in New York City.
  Former call number: Uncat MSS 1071
  https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&510e5e75-bfaa-4dbb-b097-8cac4315a5cc
  - Correspondence, circa 1960-2008; 345057
    Organized into three groupings: Chronological, General, and Miscellaneous.
    Correspondence consists of incoming and outgoing letters.
    - Chronological, 345085
      This group of correspondence represents letters that were housed together in boxes according to year. The overall grouping by year has been maintained and the groupings have been arranged in rough chronological order, however letters within each grouping are not arranged in any order.
      - circa 1972-1982 circa 1972-1982, 345092; 19 Folders (Box 59)
      - circa 1982-1983 circa 1982-1983, 345091; 14 Folders (Box 60)
      - circa 1984-1985 circa 1984-1985, 345090; 15 Folders (Box 61)
      - circa 1985 circa 1985, 345089; 15 Folders (Box 62)
      - circa 1987-1988 circa 1987-1988, 345088; 14 Folders (Box 63)
      - circa 1988-1994 circa 1988-1994, 345087; 14 Folders (Box 64)
      - circa 1995-2008 circa 1995-2008, 345086; 22 Folders (Box 65)
    - General, 345063
      Arranged alphabetically by correspondent or original folder heading, which appears in quotes.
      - Anderson, Gabriel, circa 1995; 345084 (Box 66)
      - Arkell, Rose and Tom, circa 1960-1968; 345083 (Box 66)
      - Averill, Brett, circa 1981; 345082 (Box 66)
      - Dramatist Guild, circa 1989-1991; 345081 (Box 66)
      - D'Urso, Joseph Paul, circa 1973; 345080 (Box 66)
      - Family correspondence, circa 1960s; 345079 (Box 66)
      - Fan mail, circa 1970s; 345078; 3 Folders (Box 66)
      - Gillespie, William, circa 1971-1974; 345077 (Box 66)
      - Kramer, Arthur, circa 1992; 345076 (Box 66)
      - Kramer, Larry, circa 1995; 345075; 3 Folders (Box 66)
      - Kramer, Liza, circa 1978; 345074 (Box 66)
      - "Letters of Recommendation", circa 1995; 345073 (Box 66)
      - McFarlane, Roger, circa 1990s; 345072 (Box 66)
      - "Mother's estate", circa 1996; 345071 (Box 66)
      - "The New York Times", circa 1980s; 345070 (Box 66)
      - Newspaper articles, circa 1984-1987; 345069 (Box 66)
      - Prager, Robert, circa 1987-1990; 345068; 2 Folders (Box 67)
      - Rainey, Fred, circa 1976-1978; 345067 (Box 67)
      - Umans, Richard, circa 1977-1985; 345066 (Box 67)
      - Writers Guild of America, circa 1990-1995; 345065 (Box 67)
      - Yale University, circa 1980s-1990s; 345064 (Box 67)
    - Miscellaneous, 345058
      - Miscellaneous, circa 1970s-1980s; 345062; 9 Folders (Box 67)
        Arranged in a very rough chronological order with original groupings left intact.
      - Miscellaneous, circa 1980s-1990s; 345061; 13 Folders (Box 68)
      - Miscellaneous, circa 1980s-1990s; 345060; 10 Folders (Box 69)
        Includes two audiocassettes: "What's Going On?" by Paul Willcocks (circa 1985) and an unlabeled cassette (circa 1980s).
        Access to original audiocassettes is restricted. Reference copies may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
      - Miscellaneous, circa 1980s-1990s; 345059; 12 Folders (Box 70)
  - Writings, circa 1937-2005; 344974
    This series contains material relating to the creation of Kramer's writings and consists primarily of numerous copies of various drafts and manuscripts of his plays, screenplays, and books. For material relating more to the production, publication, and reception of Kramer's writings, see Writings Files.
    Organized into four groupings according to genre: Plays; Screenplays; Books; and Shorter Works and Other Writings.
    - Plays, 345034
      Arranged alphabetically by title of work.
      - The Destiny of Me, circa 1991-1992; 345056; 19 Folders (Box 71)
      - The Destiny of Me, circa 1987-1993; 345055; 15 Folders (Box 72)
        Includes early versions of The Destiny of Me, variously titled "Children Afraid of the Night" and "Furniture of Home".
      - The Destiny of Me, circa 1987-1991; 345054; 14 Folders (Box 73)
      - The Destiny of Me, circa 1987-1990s; 345053; 15 Folders (Box 74)
      - The Destiny of Me, rehearsal draft, circa 1992; 345052 (Box 75)
      - Just Say No: A Play About a Farce, circa 1980s; 345051; 2 Folders (Box 75)
      - Just Say No: A Play About a Farce, circa 1986-1988; 345050; 14 Folders (Box 76)
        Included are early versions of Just Say No: A Play About a Farce, titled "First Lady".
      - Just Say No: A Play About a Farce, circa 1988; 345049; 14 Folders (Box 77)
      - "A Minor Dark Age", circa 1970s; 345048; 2 Folders (Box 77)
      - "A Minor Dark Age", circa 1976; 345047; 2 Folders (Box 78)
      - The Normal Heart, circa 1984-1986; 345046; 11 Folders (Box 78)
        Includes drafts of screenplay based on the original The Normal Heart script.
      - The Normal Heart, circa1985-1995; 345045; 21 Folders (Box 79)
        Includes some press clippings.
      - The Normal Heart, circa 1984-1986; 345044; 14 Folders (Box 80)
      - The Normal Heart, circa 1980s-1990s; 345043; 8 Folders (Box 81)
        Includes press material, correspondence, royalty information and press clippings.
      - The Normal Heart, circa 1984; 345042; 8 Folders (Box 82)
      - The Normal Heart, circa 1986-2005; 345041; 19 Folders (Box 83)
      - The Normal Heart, circa 1986-2005; 345040; 18 Folders (Box 84)
      - The Normal Heart, circa 1984-1994; 345039; 17 Folders (Box 85)
      - The Normal Heart, circa 1984-1986; 345038; 12 Folders (Box 86)
      - The Normal Heart, circa 1984-1986; 345037; 4 Folders (Box 87)
      - "Sissies' Scrapbook", circa 1974-1975; 345036; 13 Folders (Box 87)
      - "Sissies' Scrapbook", circa 1973-1975; 345035; 16 Folders (Box 88)
        Includes early versions of "Sissies' Scrapbook," titled "Four Friends."
    - Screenplays, 345011
      - "American Classic", circa 1970s; 345033; 12 Folders (Box 89)
        Included are other versions of American Classic, titled "Sea Change".
      - "Hammerhead", circa 1966; 345032; 4 Folders (Box 90)
      - "Hands Across the Sea", circa 1980s; 345031; 4 Folders (Box 90)
      - "Head Games", circa 1969-1970s; 345030; 12 Folders (Box 90)
        Included are other versions of Head Games, titled "Forbidden Colors."
      - "Head Games", circa 1970; 345029; 9 Folders (Box 91)
      - "Helen and Harry", circa 1973; 345028; 3 Folders (Box 91)
        Included are some written material, as well as magazines used for research.
      - "Here We Go Round the Mulberry Bush", circa 1965-1967; 345027; 4 Folders (Box 91)
      - "Here We Go Round the Mulberry Bush", circa 1965-1967; 345026; 2 Folders (Box 92)
      - "Just a Love Nest", circa 1970s; 345025; 6 Folders (Box 92)
        Included are two printed items: Snow White and the Seven Dwarfs: A Tale From The Brothers Grimm, translated by Randall Jarrell and Walt Disney's Snow White and the Seven Dwarfs.
      - "Late Bloomers", circa 1980; 345024; 3 Folders (Box 92)
      - "Lost Horizon", circa 1937-1972; 345023; 20 Folders (Box 93)
        Includes a copy of the 1937 Robert Riskin screenplay of Lost Horizon, directed by Frank Capra.
      - "The Loudest Cry", circa 1961; 345022; 3 Folders (Box 94)
      - "Misc notes/cards", 345021 (Box 94)
      - "Never Die Poor", circa 1969; 345020; 7 Folders (Box 94)
      - "Passing Through", circa 1971; 345019 (Box 94)
      - "The Rich Get Richer", circa 1970s; 345018; 4 Folders (Box 94)
      - "The Rich Get Richer", circa 1970s; 345017; 5 Folders (Box 95)
      - "Robert Never Was", 345016 (Box 95)
      - "Stay Hungry", circa 1972-1973; 345015; 9 Folders (Box 95)
      - Women in Love, circa 1967-1969; 345014; 15 Folders (Box 96)
      - Women in Love, circa 1967-1969; 345013; 14 Folders (Box 96)
      - "Unknown Script", 345012 (Box 96)
    - Books, 345001
      - Faggots, circa 1977-1978; 345010; 17 Folders (Box 97)
      - Faggots, circa 1975-1978; 345009; 17 Folders (Box 98)
      - Faggots, circa 1977-1978; 345008; 15 Folders (Box 99)
      - Faggots, circa 1977-1978; 345007; 17 Folders (Box 100)
      - Faggots, circa 1977-1978; 345006; 13 Folders (Box 101)
      - Faggots, circa 1977-1978; 345005; 15 Folders (Box 102)
      - Faggots, circa 1977-1994; 345004; 8 Folders (Box 103)
      - Reports from the Holocaust, circa 1989-1995; 345003; 12 Folders (Box 104)
      - The Tragedy of Today's Gays, circa 2004-2005; 345002; 2 Folders (Box 104)
    - Shorter Works and Other Writings, 344975
      - "The Abbots" and "The Lady and the Hard Hat", 345000 (Box 105)
      - "Adam and Company", circa 1971; 344999 (Box 105)
      - "The Big Three at Yalta", circa 1970s; 344998; 13 Folders (Box 105)
      - "The Big Three at Yalta", circa 1970s; 344997; 2 Folders (Box 106)
      - "Create Yourself A New Image, Charlie", circa 1965; 344996 (Box 106)
      - "Day of Atonement", circa 1981; 344995; 11 Folders (Box 106)
      - "The Department Store", circa 1969; 344994; 2 Folders (Box 106)
      - "Do Two Dead Homosexuals Equal One Dead Prostitute?", circa 1981; 344993 (Box 107)
      - "Envelope scrap", 344992 (Box 107)
      - "Early Writings [poetry and prose]", circa 1957-; 344991 (Box 107)
      - "Fear Comedy and Larry -Ellen 16c", 344990 (Box 107)
      - "Freshman Year", 344989; 3 Folders (Box 107)
      - "A Gambol Off the Deep End", circa 1956; 344988 (Box 107)
      - "Journal of the Plague Years", circa 1987; 344987 (Box 107)
      - "LA notes and story notecards", 344986 (Box 107)
      - "The Lady and the Hard Hat", circa 1973; 344985 (Box 107)
      - "The Ladies who Lunch", circa 1971; 344984; 6 Folders (Box 107)
      - Miscellaneous, 344983 (Box 107)
      - Miscellaneous poems, 344982 (Box 107)
      - "Mrs. Tefillin", circa 1980s; 344981 (Box 107)
      - "Mrs. Tefillin", circa 1980s-1996; 344980; 11 Folders (Box 108)
      - "Only Yesterday", 344979 (Box 108)
      - "The Sexual Education of an American Male", circa 1979; 344978; 2 Folders (Box 108)
      - Various, circa 1978-1980; 344977 (Box 108)
      - Unidentified Manuscript, 344976; 2 Folders (Box 108)
  - Writing Files, circa 1968-2004; 344948
    This series consists of material relating to the production, publication, and reception of Kramer's writings (including plays, screenplays, and books). Material includes correspondence, press material, clippings, reviews, royalty statements, notes, and photographs. For material relating more to the creation of Kramer's writings, see Writings, Drafts and Manuscripts.
    - "BBC 'Arena' documentary on Larry Kramer", circa 1990s; 344973 (Box 109)
    - The Destiny of Me, circa1990-1993; 344972; 16 Folders (Box 109)
    - The Destiny of Me, circa 1992-1997; 344971; 18 Folders (Box 110)
      Includes photographic slides.
    - Faggots, circa 1978-1979; 344970; 4 Folders (Box 110)
    - Faggots, circa 1979-1995; 344969; 9 Folders (Box 111)
    - "First Hero", circa 1994; 344968 (Box 111)
    - "Freshman Year", 344967 (Box 111)
    - Just Say No: A Play about a Farce, circa 1988-1989; 344966; 2 Folders (Box 111)
    - Just Say No: A Play about a Farce, circa 1988-1995; 344965; 13 Folders (Box 112)
    - "Kramer biography", circa 1995; 344964 (Box 112)
    - "Kramer vs. Kramer", circa 1989; 344963 (Box 112)
    - "Marvin's Room", circa 1992; 344962 (Box 112)
    - Mass, Larry, circa 1996-1997; 344961 (Box 112)
    - "Noel and Cole", circa 1995; 344960 (Box 112)
    - The Normal Heart, circa 1982-1985; 344959; 19 Folders (Box 113)
    - The Normal Heart, circa 1985-1986; 344958; 14 Folders (Box 114)
    - The Normal Heart, circa 1985-1988; 344957; 13 Folders (Box 115)
    - The Normal Heart, circa 1986-1990s; 344956; 15 Folders (Box 116)
    - The Normal Heart, circa 1991-1997; 344955; 16 Folders (Box 117)
      Includes two audiocassettes of "The Normal Heart" (circa 1993).
      Access to original audiocassettes is restricted. Reference copies may be requested.
    - "Notes and Photos", circa 1995; 344954; 5 Folders (Box 117)
    - "Penguin Book of Gay Short Fiction", circa 1993; 344953; 2 Folders (Box 117)
    - Reports From the Holocaust, circa 1989-1990s; 344952; 16 Folders (Box 118)
    - "Sissies' Scrapbook", circa 1975; 344951; 2 Folders (Box 118)
    - Women in Love, circa 1967-1971; 344950; 25 Folders (Box 119)
    - Women in Love, circa 1968-2004; 344949; 5 Folders (Box 120)
  - Professional Papers and Research Material, circa 1950s-2006; 344795
    This series consists of a wide range of material relating broadly to Kramer's various professional activities, including his film work, his AIDS advocacy and activism, especially his work with Gay Men's Health Crisis (GMHC) and AIDS Coalition to Unleash Power (ACT UP), and his non-literary writing. Material includes correspondence, printed material, notes and notebooks, research material, typescripts of articles and speeches, clippings of interviews and articles by and about Kramer, and other office files.
    Organized into eight groupings: Notebooks; Film Project Files; Early Files; AIDS General; AIDS Activism; Research Material; Interviews, Articles, and Speeches; and Other Files.
    Within the groupings, files are not arranged in any particular order.
    - Notebooks, 344946
      - Notebooks, circa 1970s; 344947; 13 Folders (Box 121)
    - Film Project Files, 344918
      - Outline, circa 1980; 344945 (Box 122)
      - Film Articles, circa 1969; 344944 (Box 122)
      - Variety, circa 1971; 344943 (Box 122)
      - Film Correspondence, circa 1972-1973; 344942 (Box 122)
      - Women in Love, circa 1967-1971; 344941; 24 Folders (Box 122)
      - Forbidden Colors, circa 1968-1971; 344940; 12 Folders (Box 123)
      - Lost Horizon, circa 1971-1973; 344939; 5 Folders (Box 124)
      - Mo Rothman's Production Report, circa 1960-1961; 344938 (Box 124)
      - Photographs - Larry Kramer, 344937 (Box 124)
      - Film Notebooks, 344936 (Box 124)
      - Film - Miscellaneous printed, 344935 (Box 124)
      - "Transatlantic View", article for Publisher's Weekly, circa 1966; 344934; 2 Folders (Box 124)
      - Late Bloomers, circa 1980-1982; 344933 (Box 124)
      - St. Krebs, proposed TV comedy, circa 1982; 344932 (Box 124)
      - Beautiful and the Damned, film project, circa 1969-1971; 344931 (Box 124)
      - Columbia Sudios Film Proposals, circa 1956-1965; 344930 (Box 124)
      - "Ideas", circa 1971; 344929 (Box 124)
      - "Americans in England", 344928 (Box 124)
      - Albermarle Productions, Women in Love, circa 1968-1969; 344927; 4 Folders (Box 124)
      - "U A Cross-Collateralisation", Women in Love, 344926 (Box 124)
      - "Moving Day", circa 1973; 344925 (Box 124)
      - Financial, circa 1980s; 344924; 2 Folders (Box 125)
      - De Stael Project, circa 1971; 344923 (Box 125)
      - "Possible Projects", correspondence, circa 1970; 344922 (Box 125)
      - "III", circa 1976; 344921 (Box 125)
      - "Stay Hungry", research, circa 1972; 344920 (Box 125)
      - "The Color of Money", correspondence, 344919 (Box 125)
    - Early Files, 344883
      - Student papers, circa 1952-1955; 344917 (Box 125)
      - Portrait photos, circa 1950s; 344916 (Box 125)
      - Resume and job applications, circa 1950s; 344915 (Box 125)
      - Kamp Kohut yearbooks and High School and College commencement programs, circa 1950-1957; 344914 (Box 125)
      - Financial, circa 1950s; 344913 (Box 125)
      - Will, circa 1972; 344912 (Box 125)
      - Correspondence, circa 1966-1969; 344911 (Box 125)
      - Clippings, 1968; 344910 (Box 125)
      - Personal, 344909 (Box 125)
      - Marrakech, circa 1969; 344908 (Box 125)
      - Family Correspondence, circa 1960; 344907 (Box 125)
      - "N.Y.", 344906 (Box 125)
      - Clippings, circa 1960s; 344905 (Box 125)
      - Notes, circa 1970; 344904 (Box 125)
      - Correspondence - Fifield, Barringer, circa 1970-1972; 344903 (Box 126)
      - Correspondence - Greenstein, Martin, circa 1972; 344902 (Box 126)
      - Correspondence - Caricatures, circa 1966; 344901 (Box 126)
      - "Bob Damron's Address Book", circa 1971; 344900 (Box 126)
      - "Journal to Journal", fragments, circa 1971-1972; 344899 (Box 126)
      - Photo portraits, circa 1973; 344898 (Box 126)
      - "Parties", 344897 (Box 126)
      - "Humor", 344896 (Box 126)
      - Topical - Loeb Drama Center, Harvard, circa 1971-1976; 344895 (Box 126)
      - Scotland, circa 1970s; 344894 (Box 126)
      - Clippings, circa 1960s-1970s; 344893; 2 Folders (Box 126)
      - Op-Ed piece, regarding Harvey Milk, circa 1978; 344892 (Box 126)
      - Yale 25th Reunion article, 344891 (Box 126)
      - "Dog paperwork", circa 1979-1980; 344890 (Box 126)
      - Press clippings, circa 1969-1970; 344889; 2 Folders (Box 126)
      - "To Sleep Til Tuesday", circa 1953; 344888 (Box 126)
      - "Astrological", circa 1974; 344887 (Box 126)
      - "Whore House", planned novel, circa 1979; 344886 (Box 126)
      - "Is Homosexuality a Form?," New School for Social Research Course, circa 1980; 344885; 2 Folders (Box 126)
      - Loose Letters, circa 1980; 344884; 2 Folders (Box 126)
    - AIDS General, 344856
      - AIDS, miscellaneous correspondence, circa 1993; 344882; 3 Folders (Box 127)
      - Community Research Initiative, 344881 (Box 127)
      - Darrell Yates Rist, 344880 (Box 127)
      - Salk Institute, 344879 (Box 127)
      - Royal Marks Foundation, 344878 (Box 127)
      - The Advocate, circa 1990s; 344877; 7 Folders (Box 127)
      - Project Inform, circa 1995; 344876 (Box 128)
      - Lamda, circa 1994; 344875 (Box 128)
      - Broadway Cares, circa 1994; 344874 (Box 128)
      - TAG, circa 1995; 344873 (Box 128)
      - Political Writings, circa 1990-1991; 344872 (Box 128)
      - General Interest, circa 1989-1992; 344871 (Box 128)
      - AIDS, circa 1991-1993; 344870 (Box 128)
      - Future Direction in AIDS Research, circa 1993; 344869 (Box 128)
      - Hepatitis, circa 1991; 344868 (Box 128)
      - Time, circa 1983-1993; 344867 (Box 128)
      - Misc Letters regarding AIDS, circa 1994-1997; 344866 (Box 128)
      - POZ, circa 1994-1997; 344865 (Box 128)
      - GMHC (Gay Men's Health Crisis), circa 1995; 344864 (Box 128)
      - PWA, circa 1996; 344863 (Box 128)
      - ACT UP, circa 1993-1994; 344862 (Box 128)
      - D.P.N., circa 1994; 344861 (Box 128)
      - Common Cause, circa 1996; 344860; 3 Folders (Box 128)
      - Larry Kramer - Miscellaneous writings, circa 1989-1990; 344859 (Box 128)
      - Philadelphia, the movie (1994), circa 1994; 344858; 4 Folders (Box 129)
      - "Other Authors", circa 1995; 344857; 4 Folders (Box 129)
    - AIDS Activism, 344851
      - Gay Men's Heath Crisis, circa 1983-1991; 344855; 7 Folders (Box 129)
        Includes an award - an engraved metal tray - given to Larry Kramer by the Gay Men's Health Crisis.
      - ACT UP, circa 1990-1991; 344854; 7 Folders (Box 129)
      - ACT UP, circa 1990-1991; 344853; 20 Folders (Box 130)
      - ACT UP, circa 1990s; 344852; 2 Folders (Box 131)
    - Research Material, 344847
      - Research Material, 344849; 2 Folders (Box 131)
        Includes clippings, printed material, and notes pertaining to various subjects, including Roy Cohn and Proust.
      - Research Material, 344848; 25 Folders (Box 132)
    - Interviews, Articles, and Speeches, 344809
      - Medical writings - AIDS, 344846 (Box 132)
      - New York Times, correspondence and clippings, circa 1988-1993; 344845; 4 Folders (Box 133)
      - Out Week, correspondence and clippings, circa 1990; 344844 (Box 133)
      - Ed Koch, correspondence and clippings, circa 1989-1990; 344843 (Box 133)
      - New York Native, circa 1989; 344842 (Box 133)
      - Village Voice, circa 1989; 344841 (Box 133)
      - "Articles for The Advocate", circa 1991-1995; 344840 (Box 133)
      - "Article, A Good News / Bad News AIDS Joke", circa 1996; 344839 (Box 133)
      - Interviews of and Articles by Larry Kramer, 344838; 11 Folders (Box 133)
      - AIDS: The War is Lost, circa 1990; 344837 (Box 133)
      - Architectural Digest, Feature on Larry Kramer, circa 1995; 344836; 2 Folders (Box 134)
      - Science Magazine letter, 344835 (Box 134)
      - Transmission, circa 1996; 344834 (Box 134)
      - Key West Literary Seminar, 344833 (Box 134)
      - America Academy of Arts and Letters, Award, circa 1996; 344832; 2 Folders (Box 134)
      - Writers Contract, "The New AIDS Crisis", circa 1997; 344831 (Box 134)
      - Current biography, circa 1994; 344830 (Box 134)
      - ICM (letter to prospective agent), circa 1996; 344829 (Box 134)
      - Interviews, circa 1993-1994; 344828 (Box 134)
      - New York Public Library, correspondence regarding manuscript collection, circa 1992-1993; 344827 (Box 134)
      - Quotes, correspondence, circa 1995-1996; 344826 (Box 134)
      - Rudin, Scott - correspondence, circa 1996-1997; 344825 (Box 134)
      - Writing Requests, circa 1997; 344824 (Box 134)
      - Speeches, circa 1991-1993; 344823; 3 Folders (Box 134)
      - Speech notes, 344822 (Box 134)
      - Memorials, circa 1993-1994; 344821 (Box 134)
      - Lectures, 344820; 5 Folders (Box 134)
      - GMHC: Interview with Larry Kramer, transcript, circa 1994; 344819 (Box 135)
      - New York magazine, Larry Kramer interview, circa 1998; 344818 (Box 135)
      - Albany Speech, circa 2000; 344817 (Box 135)
        Includes a transcript of a speech, delivered by Larry Kramer in 1994 and electronically annotated by Kramer in 2000.
      - The Advocate, letters to editor regarding Larry Kramer article, circa 1997; 344816 (Box 135)
      - Notebook, Gay essays, 344815 (Box 135)
      - Writing, "The Bloods", 344814 (Box 135)
      - Writing, "The Redfern Document", 344813 (Box 135)
      - "Nuremberg Trials for AIDS", circa 2006; 344812 (Box 135)
      - Notebook, "First Lady, or See America First", 344811 (Box 135)
      - Notebook, "Old Age", 344810 (Box 135)
    - Other Files, 344796
      - Notebook - Dawidowicz in commentary, Asylum, 344808 (Box 135)
      - AIDS Treatment Activists Conference Binder, circa 1990; 344807 (Box 135)
      - Larry Kramer Initiative, Yale University, circa 1996-1997; 344806; 5 Folders (Box 135)
      - The Destiny of Me, Reviews, circa 2002; 344805 (Box 136)
      - Filofax pages, circa 2004; 344804 (Box 136)
      - Printed, AIDS-related, 344803; 2 Folders (Box 136)
      - Miscellaneous notes and writings, 344802 (Box 136)
      - Appointment Calendar, circa 2004-2005; 344801 (Box 136)
      - Lesbian and Gay Studies at Yale, circa 2005; 344800; 2 Folders (Box 136)
      - Filofax, circa 2006; 344799 (Box 136)
      - Name Tags, 344798 (Box 136)
      - Rolodex (rotating index), circa 1970s-1980s; 344797 (Box 137)
      - Kramer computer disks, accompanying documentation (Box 136)
  - Personal and Other Papers, circa 1925-2003; 344697
    Organized into six groupings: Family Papers; Household Papers; Medical Records; Other Papers; Printed Material; and Photographs.
    - Family Papers, 344760
      Includes material relating to Kramer's family, including his mother Rea, his father George, and his brother Arthur.
      - Album, 344794
      - Art Prints, 344793
      - "The Brecky 1944", yearbook and photographs, circa 1944; 344792 (Box 138)